[Music]
[Music] From here only
road trip pie apan ko tax upgrade
current drought correct suffix big and small
abstract pie apan round kar ghutiye chosen
where aapadon ko given Uber future tapay ticket
and current point is sharp
prastuthechi ICICI Pra one jojo na
where aapanon ko immediately provide ayo
first sir Kimba first and start start
strange
zodiac policy
Bhideme bhi to aaya spring apan kar which
on Z Shayari 100 bioscope men per year
one's target Uncle
and 19 and maturity Boys shobachan to
first award Saraswati
[Music]
Jyoti to future tapayi accumulation family to
peace Tevis to humility commission also Ganpat
chayankari example form quickly Tankara
commission one to 11 years dogy side some where there was
etc. Shayari from this WhatsApp to 8 to 1.7
[Music]
this is each plan policy